{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Popcorn Ceiling Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40367/":{"taskOID":40367,"originalTaskOID":40367,"setID":661,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500765,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"What is the nature of this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201004,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","answerDisplayText":"Add popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201005,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","answerDisplayText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4968,"questionDisplayText":"Home Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the home? (In years)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200795,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"10 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"10 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17646,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"20 - 30 years","answerDisplayText":"20 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9073,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"30 - 45 years","answerDisplayText":"30 - 45 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200796,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Over 45 years","answerDisplayText":"Over 45 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4753,"questionDisplayText":"Number of rooms affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms are being affected?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-4","answerDisplayText":"2-4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10","answerDisplayText":"5-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire house","answerDisplayText":"Entire house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500765,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"What is the nature of this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201004,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","answerDisplayText":"Add popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201005,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","answerDisplayText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":201004,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","answerDisplayText":"Add popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201005,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","answerDisplayText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4968,"questionDisplayText":"Home Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the home? (In years)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200795,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"10 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"10 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17646,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"20 - 30 years","answerDisplayText":"20 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9073,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"30 - 45 years","answerDisplayText":"30 - 45 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200796,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Over 45 years","answerDisplayText":"Over 45 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200795,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"10 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"10 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17646,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"20 - 30 years","answerDisplayText":"20 - 30 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9073,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"30 - 45 years","answerDisplayText":"30 - 45 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200796,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Over 45 years","answerDisplayText":"Over 45 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4753,"questionDisplayText":"Number of rooms affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms are being affected?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-4","answerDisplayText":"2-4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10","answerDisplayText":"5-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire house","answerDisplayText":"Entire house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-4","answerDisplayText":"2-4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10","answerDisplayText":"5-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire house","answerDisplayText":"Entire house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40367/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40367,"taskName":"Popcorn Acoustic Ceiling Texture - Apply, Repair or Remove","taskDescription":"Apply, Repair or Remove a Popcorn Acoustic Ceiling Texture","xmTaskDescriptor":"Popcorn Ceiling Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":346,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Popcorn Texture replacement vaulted wood","textMessagingName":"Popcorn Ceiling","rolloverLongDesc":"Lightweight little bits of fluff are mixed into the paint \u0026 the machine spatters it at the ceiling to quickly create a random textured ceiling. One of the advantages is that it can be used to cover up imperfections in the ceiling.","rolloverShortDesc":"Special equipment used for textured ceilings.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Apply or Remove a Popcorn Acoustic Ceiling Texture.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Popcorn Ceiling Removal \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Popcorn Ceiling Tile Repair, Installation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":1,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Popcorn Acoustic Ceiling Apply, Repair or Remove","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Popcorn Acoustic Ceiling Texture - Apply, Repair or Remove","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Popcorn Ceiling Project","urlName":"Popcorn-Acoustic-Ceiling-Texture-Apply-or-Remove","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Popcorn Ceiling Removal \u0026 Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs","searchKeywords":"Popcorn,Texture,replacement,vaulted,wood,tiles,removal,Apply,Ceiling,Acoustic","emcCategoryOid":-12012,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":661,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}